and back home nmg that's the nation
media group has partnered with
prudential and prudence foundation to
bring awareness on road safety measures
this initiative comes after a disturbing
surge in the number of lives lost
through road accidents according to the
national transport and safety authority
there has been a 17.3
increase in accidents in the past five
years hence the need to create awareness
and improve safety on the roads
we have purposed to design create and
share information on road safety and use
through a campaign called safe steps by
partnering with the nation media group
one of the leading media houses in kenya
and the region we are confident that we
will be able to share the life-saving
gospel of safe views of the road by both
motorists and pedestrians it's always
about the statistics
it's it's always a nameless man who was
hit
a nameless but a border rider
a nameless child
if you're lucky
the family will be named but it's the
the truth comes home to the families
that are affected and the people that
are left to deal with the anguish and
the pain we all have a role to play in
rhodes safely and we hope that these
collective efforts to which we remain
committed for the long term will help
drive greater road safety across the
country